esnips.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY  
---  
Thank you for visiting www.esnips.com (together with all other websites operated by eSnips Ltd. or its affiliates, the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the [Terms of Use](http://www.esnips.com/statments/terms.jsp).  
   
Introduction  
  
We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. 

Personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address or other contact information.

Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information which is publicly available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with certain services given under the Site, you must create an account (“Account”) and provide us with your email address and password that you will use for your Account (“Requested Details”). We shall then send you an email to your email address to instruct you how to confirm your registration. We may request additional Personal Information in the future.

If you have an Account you may, if you wish, add more information about yourself, such as pictures, videos, your age, time zone, country of residence and occupation (“Your Profile”). 

We use Personal Information for the following purposes: to identify and authenticate your access to eSnips’ services that you are authorized to access, to provide you with the services provided under the Site, to improve our services to you and to contact you.  

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies   
  
Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your e-mail address and the password of your account, to gain access to certain parts of the Site. 

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.  

Information Sharing with Others   
  
Social DNA Questionnaire: If you choose to share Your Profile with other users of the Site that have participated in a “Social DNA Questionnaire”, we shall display the details as explained in the [Social DNA Terms of Use](http://www.esnips.com/statments/socialDNATerms.jsp).   

Public Information: When you create an account on eSnips, certain information that you provide is visible to other users of the Site. We shall display the following details about you: (i) Your Profile; (ii) the display name that was generated to you by eSnips automatically when you signed up (or the subsequent display name which you selected) and; (iii) the e-mail address that you provided on sign-up, provided, however that you agreed to make it public. When users access Your Profile as set forth herein we record and display next to Your Profile the number of users that view Your Profile. 

When you create a folder you determine if such folder is classified as Public, Group or Private as detailed below:

1\. Public Folder: If you choose that your folder will be classified as Public Folder we shall also display such Public Folder and insert link from Your Profile to such Public Folder. Public Folders are visible to every user of the site. 

2\. Group Folder: You may invite particular people to access a Group Folder via email. Your email address shall be visible to such people that you have invited to access a specific Group Folder. If the people that visit a Group Folder are also users of eSnips, their display name will also be visible along with their email address. You can create several Group Folders, each with its own list of members. 

The viewing of the Group Folder by the people that you invite is recorded by eSnips. We display to invited people the following information:

  * How many people were invited to view the Group Folder
  * A list of the people that view the Group Folder
  * The time when the Group Folder was viewed by that specific person who was invited 

3\. Private Folder: A private folder is only visible to you, only when you sign into your account.  

Information Sharing with and Disclosure to Non-Users  
  
We do not rent or sell your Personal Information, but if you post online Personal Information in any place that is viewable by the general public, you may receive unsolicited messages.

We may share anonymous demographic data and related usage information with business partners. This information does not contain any Personal Information that can identify an individual user. 

Generally, eSnips does not share Personal Information about any user with any individual, company or other entity without that user’s consent, except to provide products or services the user has requested. But we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances:

  * We may be legally required to disclose Personal Information, for instance in order to comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal processes, to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend ourselves against legal claims;
  * It may be necessary to share Personal Information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eSnips’ Terms of Use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law;
  * We may need to transfer information about our users including Personal Information if eSnips is acquired by another company or merges with another company.

When you register with us, your Personal Information and other data will be stored and processed in the United States and this information may be subject to the laws of these jurisdictions.  

Choice  
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to us. The notices we will provide where we collect Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you including but not limited to uploading files or posting comments.   
   
Access/Accuracy  
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may check Your Profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information.  
   
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites  
Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.  
   
Children's Privacy  
The Site is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.  
   
Security of Your Account Information  
We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Information. Nevertheless, Personal Information or other information which you upload to the Site may be corrupted or irretrievable. You understand that eSnips has no liability for any such loss of information, photos or other data.  
   
Your Privacy Rights  
eSnips' Privacy Policy is to share personal information only with the owner's informed consent. If you have further inquires regarding eSnips' Information Sharing Practices, please let us know. The designated contact for these queries is **privacy AT esnips.com**  
   
In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy  
In the event that eSnips is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.  
   
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
  
By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to eSnips' processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. eSnips may update this policy at any time for any reason. If a change significantly affects how we handle personal information, we will either send a notice to the primary email address specified in your eSnips account or place a prominent notice on our site.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and eSnips’ Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy please send us email to privacy AT esnips.com or you can contact us at:

Logia Media Ltd.  
POB 4010  
3 Hasadnaot St,  
Herzeliya Pituach, 46140  
Israel

**While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.**

Last modified: August 21, 2007
